{
    "data_info": {
        "documentID": "J_FOOD_013988",
        "source": "도서",
        "writer": "임선영",
        "ISBN_ISNN": "979-11-8651-740-6",
        "version": "초판",
        "source_language": "ko",
        "translator": "파파고",
        "source_url": "셰프의 맛집",
        "collectedDate": "2023-11-03",
        "publishedDate": "2015-12-02",
        "domain": "음식점",
        "title": "치얼업"
    },
    "text": "マンゴヨーグルトスムージー,6,500ウォン/ミントチョコラテ,5,500ウォン/アイスアメリカノ,3,500ウォン/カプチノ,4,000ウォン/ブルベリ・スムディ,5,500ウォン/タルギ・スムディ,6,000ウォン/モカラテ,5,500ウォン/エスプレソ,2,500ウォン/シナモンマルチャ・ラテ,5,500ウォン/カラメル・マキアト,5,000ウォン/アイスティ,3,500ウォン/レモネード,4,000ウォン/林檎ジュース,4,000ウォン/オレンジジュス,4,500ウォン/トマト・ジュス,4,500ウォン/キウイエード,5,000ウォン/イチゴエード,5,500ウォン/柚茶,3,500ウォン/ミルク,3,000ウォン。",
    "QA": [
        {
            "question": "マンゴヨーグルトスムージーはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "マンゴヨーグルトスムージーは６５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ミントチョコラテはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ミントチョコラテは５５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "アイスアメリカノはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "アイスアメリカノは３５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "カプチノはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "カプチノは４０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ブルベリ・スムディはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ブルベリ・スムディは５５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "タルギ・スムディはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "タルギ・スムディは６０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "モカラテはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "モカラテは５５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "エスプレソはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "エスプレソは２５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "シナモンマルチャ・ラテはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "シナモンマルチャ・ラテは５５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "カラメル・マキアトはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "カラメル・マキアトは５０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "アイスティはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "アイスティは３５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "レモネードはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "レモネードは４０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "林檎ジュースはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "林檎ジュースは４０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "オレンジジュスはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "オレンジジュスは４５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "トマト・ジュスはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "トマト・ジュスは４５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "キウイエードはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "キウイエードは５０００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "イチゴエードはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "イチゴエードは５５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "柚茶はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "柚茶は３５００ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ミルクはいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ミルクは３０００ウォンです。"
        }
    ],
    "word_Count": {
        "text": 231,
        "QA": 449
    }
}